Love and can hurt, Love and can hurt sometimes, but it's the only thing that
I know, when it gets hard, you know it can get hard sometimes, it is the only thing that makes us feel alive.
We keep this love in a photograph, we make these memories for ourselves, where our eyes are never closing, hearts are never broken, times forever frozen still.
So you can keep me inside the pocket of your ripped jeans, holding me close until I made you won't ever be alone.
Wait for me to come home. Love and can heal, Love and can mend your soul, and it's the only thing that I know, know.
I swear it will get easier, remember that I put every piece of work in it, and it's the only thing we take with us when we die.
We keep this love in a photograph, we make these memories for ourselves, where our eyes are never closing, hearts are never broken, times forever frozen still.
So you can keep me inside the pocket of your ripped jeans, holding me close until I made you won't ever be alone.
And what you hurt me, that's okay baby, only words complete, inside these pages you just hold me, no one ever let you burn.
Wait for me to come home.
We can fit, we inside the pocket of your ripped jeans, holding me close until I made you won't ever be alone.
And what you hurt me, that's okay baby, only words complete, inside these pages you just hold me, no one ever let you burn.
And I'll remember how you kissed me, under the lamppost back on 6th street, hearing you whisper through the phone.
You're at the top of the mountain.
Wait for me to come home.